Aaaaaahhh!
Goddammit!
How could you let yourself give
in to the Synthesis Ritual?
You forget why you're a swordsman?
Why you left Rulid and came
to Senator in the first place?
You're here for Alice!
You're here to take
her back home with you!
Oh, my love!
Oh, my love! Oh, my love! Huh?
Ah! Ah! Oh!
Thank you
so
much
for
watching.
I'll
see you
next time.
Yu-Gi-Oh, you and me never
had a full-on fight before.
I used to think about who'd win.
If the day ever came, we got
to cross swords for real.
To tell the truth, I knew you'd beat
me one day, but that ain't today.
I'll show him a move he's
never seen me do before!
Burst element.
He is much too powerful.
I doubt this one is really your friend.
What are you talking about?
If he's been synthesized, wouldn't
that make him super strong?
That is true.
However, something is off about him.
For one who only just became an Integrity
Knight, he seems too accustomed to battle.
Incarnate arms and that
aerial element skill he just
used are far too advanced for
a newcomer to have mastered.
You should let me handle him.
I got this.
All right, buddy.
When this is over, I'll give you a name.
Just help me get through this.
En Kirito, Ugeo!
Oh, my God.
A snappy move.
It got a name?
Blade style. Stormwave.
Wait, Blade?
As in Golgorosso, Blade?
Yujiro, think back.
Do you remember the guy that
taught you how to do that?
I don't, and I don't care.
The only person I need to remember is her.
She is the reason I use my sword.
I exist to eliminate her enemies.
He's got a crystal in his head,
just like Eldrie and Alice.
Once the piety module is inserted, it
effectively blocks the links to memories.
With that, the prospective knight's
past is sealed away. The result?
A knight who is loyal to the Church
and to their creator, the Pontifex.
What memories are being blocked?
If I can figure it out and
remind him, he'll snap out of it.
No, it'll take more than words
to break Administrator's spell.
I'll pour my heart into my sword.
That'll reach him.
Hell, it's better.
QG!
I'm going to force you to
remember everyone you cared about.
Back in ruling, there's
a girl waiting for you.
Her name's Selka!
At the Swordcraft Academy, Google Rosa
was your mentor and Lina was mine!
And Tiese and Ronier!
Remember when we last saw him?
Come on, man!
You gotta remember why you came here!
It's to take Alice back home!
Remember, dammit!
Oh,
my God.
Yu-Gi-Oh!
Alice.
Do you remember her?
U-U-U-Gio.
Watch out!
Enhance armament.
Yucho, why?
I trust you took care of those
despicable traitors, Number 32.
I have them both trapped
in ice, Prime Senator, sir.
They can't go anywhere.
You don't say!
That's all well and good, my boy.
But you did not finish them off, did you?
No, Prime Senator. I did not.
My orders from the Pontifex were to
stop the traitors, not to kill them.
That won't do!
That simply won't do!
And when you speak to me,
you call me Your Excellency!
Do not forget that again, Number 32,
because if you do, I will punish
you by turning you into a horse.
And then I shall ride on your back,
shouting, Giddy up, little horsey! Giddy up!
I'll finish them off and show her
eminence It's who's more loyal.
I have returned, my lady.
Welcome back, Eugeo.
Did you complete the task
I gave you? Yes. Well done!
You deserve a reward.
Come, climb into bed with me.
All right.
As promised, I shall give
you your heart's desire.
Love for you and you alone.
Yes.
First, I should do
something about that wound.
Now then let me have a look at
your face again i found an odd
gap in your memory and that is
where i put the module convenient
but i should not have rushed
the process i'll resynthesize
you properly and then after
that you shall have your reward?
The end
Be a good boy and stay still.
This module is a vast
improvement over the old ones.
It bolsters the imagination and unlocks
advanced arts like incarnate arms.
Now relax and show me your memories again.
And this time, I'll insert it into
the memory you hold most dear.
You can't move, but you may speak.
Now, chant the spell I taught you.
Go on.
Don't tell me you've forgotten it already.
Oh, you silly thing.
Remove core protection.
How dare you!
I see you regained your senses.
I can't believe you fooled me.
I assume the little brat from the
library gave you that knife, yes?
Stab me all you want.
I am impervious to it.
No metal object can pierce my skin.
You poor child.
To reject the promise I made.
All you had to do was give yourself to
me, and I would love you back in return.
The kind of love you sought
all your life. Eternal love.
Eternal control.
And you chose to reject it like this.
Eternal love.
Eternal control.
That's right, Eugeo.
If you give yourself to me,
that thirst you've been suffering
from would be instantly quenched.
and all the confusion and fear you
harbored for so long would disappear.
But I shall give you one more chance.
Take your sword and smash that toy.
Do that, and I shall forgive your sins
and shower you with the bounty of my love.
To love is to control
and to be controlled.
If that is how you think of
it, then I feel sorry for you.
Maybe that's how you feel, starved for
love, looking all over and never finding it.
But love isn't about control,
and you don't give it to get
something like a transaction.
You give it selflessly, like
you give water to a flower.
That's love, real honest love.
What a shame.
I wanted to forgive you for your
treasonous acts against the church.
I wanted to save your soul, and
this is how you speak to me.
I could drain your life and turn
you into a jewel if I wanted,
but that would be a waste.
Instead, I'll synthesize
you by force, like her.
You mean...
That's right, sweet number 30,
the one you're so infatuated with.
She also refused to chant the
spell and it took the automated
senators days to disable her
core protection You monsters.
I didn't actually see it.
I was asleep
I'm sure it was agonizing for her.
Oh Well in the end you too
will suffer the same experience
I WILL BREAK THROUGH!
That sword.
Oh, now I see.
Save me!
Please, your eminence!
I need assistance here!
You traitor!
This little bastard
betrayed you, your eminence!
He said he trapped Number 30 and that
other rogue, but he didn't even...
Let go! Let go!
Kirito...
What's up? Yu-Gi-Oh.
Sorry.
I gave in to Administrator's temptation
and tried to kill you both.
I wanted to sacrifice
myself to atone for it.
I knew that's what you were going for.
We've been friends so long,
I can read you like a book.
You never change, do you?
Alice.
Is that her? Administrator?
Yes.
She looks the same as
she did six years ago.
Bercouli and Fanatio were just
about due for me to reset them.
But you, Alice, I've only had
you for what, six years now?
Your logic circuits don't
seem to be malfunctioning.
Perhaps that irregular unit
is influencing you. Hmm.
What is it, Alice?
If you wish to say something
to me, then just say it.
I won't get mad.
Please, speak your mind.
I will, your eminence.
As of today, the proud order of
the Integrity Knights has fallen.
All it took to bring it down
were the swords of the two
rebels at my side and the
obsession and deceit of your rule,
represented by this cathedral.
My duty is not to protect the church,
but to protect the innocent
and safeguard their peace.
It is your actions,
more than anything else,
which threaten the well-being of
the citizens of the human empire.
You!
Shut your mouth!
How dare I?
Duty, you say, you broken toy? Ha!
You knights are nothing more than dolls,
and you're guilty as you put it...
Fascinating.
It isn't a logic circuit error after all.
And her piety module is still functioning.
Which means she must have
disabled the code 871
that was installed for
me by her own volition,
rather than by sudden emotion.
That thing in her eyes called code 871?
I won't know how it happened
until I run an analysis.
Now then, Chudelkin.
Since I am generous,
I shall give you the chance to
restore your tattered reputation.
Use your sacred arts and
deal with those three.
But your eminence!
Your gloriousness!
Yes, what is it?
For the first and only time in
my many years of service to you,
I would like to present you
with a most impudent request.
I shall happily risk my life
annihilating these traitors.
However, once I have fulfilled
your wishes, would you?
Would you let me touch
your exalted body and kiss
your lips and spend one
magical night alone with you?
Please, please!
I would be most grateful if
you granted me such a delight!
Very well, Chudelkin.
I swear to the goddess Stacia,
as soon as you have
fulfilled your mission,
My body will be yours for the
taking every inch for one night.
Words cannot express the joy you've
brought me, your exalted holiness.
And I swear to you, I will
not let you down. Huh?
I am resolute and energized.
I am motivated and I am invincible!
Thermal System Call!
Generate Thermal Element!
Now I will show you my
greatest secret art!
Come forth, genie, and
burn these traitors to ash!
Alright, finally...
I can't
say that life goes on.
Oh everything turns to ash to ash.
And everything turns to dust to dust
Take my sword.
Forget me no more.
Next time, Titan of the Sword?